# **Brooklyn Chen**

## **Gameplay Programmer**

Portfolio: <a href="https://luzoko.itch.io/">https://luzoko.itch.io/</a>

Email: hi@luzoko.dev

Multi-disciplinary game developer with a focus on visuals and gameplay mechanics. Two years professional experience working with independent game studios. Skilled in programming, gameplay design, art, animation, visual effects, and collaborating with programmers and artists.

## **SKILLS:**

 Tools: Unity Engine, Godot, Git, PlasticSCM, Visual Studio Code, Clip Studio Paint, After Effects, Spine, Trello, Jira

• Languages: C#, GDScript, Java

## **EDUCATION:**

**Georgia State University**Bachelor's of Science in Computer Science
Graduated May 2020

#### **EXPERIENCE:**

#### **Princely Girl Games**

#### **Programmer**

May 2024-Present

- Leading software development efforts to port <u>The Phantom of the Black Rose Revue</u> from Ren'Py to Godot
- Recreating mechanics and animations to emulate and expand on the source material
- Planning out scene and code structure to support writing and narrative design efforts

## **Pet Golem Games**

## **Gameplay Programmer**

October 2022-Present

- Designing levels to introduce and showcase new mechanics as part of an unannounced project
- Shipped The Cauldron Kids: The Summoning of Mr. Vermicelli on Steam successfully
- Programmed minigames that integrated and interfaced with a pre-existing, actively developing codebase
- Collaborated with a fully remote team across several time zones
- Utilized a variety of Unity tools such as PlasticSCM, Rewired, Yarn Spinner, Cinemachine, etc.

#### Capgemini

#### <u>Software Engineer</u>

September 2021-May 2023

- Assisted in migrating 150+ applications from AWS EC2 hosting to EKS for a leading asset management firm
- Tested Cloud Platform APIs using JMeter for a leading asset management firm
- Trained in Java Spring Boot as a contingency worker for a leading investment bank
- Certified as an Oracle Java SE 8 Programmer I

#### **PROJECTS:**

## **SpeakEasy**

#### **Programmer & Animator**

February 2023

- Designed and integrated various UI elements for this game jam project
- Implemented a dialogue system with a stylized presentation using Yarn Spinner
- Supported programming efforts to incorporate dynamic music using FMOD Studio
- Worked with a team of eight members to plan and design the gameplay loop and code structure

### **FORGET-ME-NOT**

### Developer & Animator

August 2022

- Programmed various action game systems, including responsive controls, hitboxes, camera tracking, etc.
- Designed various enemies to engage players and teach the mechanics without using tutorials or text
- Created a number of state control systems to handle animations, enemy behavior, player controls, etc.
- Structured scripted objects to quickly load and test level data and player attacks
- Animated hand-drawn and pixel art assets to support the combat system and narrative design